En el acelerador de particulas.
(Sheldon:)Bueno, mi amigo.
(Penny:)No, no. We're not playing
some dumb, made-up game.
(Sheldon:)All games are made up.
(Sheldon:)They're not found in nature.
You don't just dig in the ground...
(Sheldon:)...come across a rich vein
of Rock 'Em Sock 'Em Robots.
(Penny:)- Pick another game.
- Why don't we do something athletic?
(Amy:)Like, go over to the university pool
and play water polo?
(Leonard:)No good, Sheldon doesn't float.
(Sheldon:)That is true.
I have a higher than normal body density.
(Sheldon:)If I run too deep a bath, I drown.
- All right, let's keep it simple. Darts?
- No, that's not fair, either.
- Why not?
- Darts is a bar game.
(Sheldon:)You've been frequenting drinking
establishments since you were of legal age.
(Leonard:)Yeah, that's when it started.
(Sheldon:)Well, regardless, she has a distinct
advantage in all tavern-based competitions.
Pool, beer-pong, wet T-shirt contests.
They're all out.